Here we go. BRING IT UP. BRING IT UP.
BRING IT UP. BRING IT UP. Bring it up.
>> Hey, couple things, man. I'LL TELL YOU
GUYS THIS. If that didn't PLAY OUT LIKE
WE TALKED ABOUT, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I'VE learned so much about team where we
did a lot of things, man. We caning
learn from it. But you found a way.
ACCOMPLISHED THE MISSION. GIVE IT UP FOR
YOURSELF. Awesome
job.
All right. WHAT A GREAT JOB BY Nate
Lind.
>> There's so many GUYS THAT I COULD
RECOGNIZE, BUT I'LL tell you what, he
ended up GETTING STITCHES BACK.
HE CAME after
listen closely on this. We all know how
lucky we ARE TO HAVE THIS GUY LEADING
THE WAY, but today goes over 60,000
yard.
We're grateful to have this guy. I love
this team, man. lot that we can learn
from. But hey, grateful for Matthew St.
>> He is him.
>> HEY, NICE JOB, MAN. NICE JOB.
>> HE IS HIM.
>> HEY, THAT'S A LOT OF FUN. I MADE A LOT
OF GREAT MEMORIES, MAN. WE GOT A BUNCH
MORE TO make here, man. That's some
right there. WAY TO FINISH IT. RAMS ON
THREE. 1 2 3
up in here tonight. Bring it up in here
tonight, guys.
>> Hey, I'll tell you what. I'm really,
really proud of you guys because that
little pitch that you guys flipped in
the SECOND HALF. THAT'S WHAT IT CAN feel
like when we really PUT IT TOGETHER ON
BOTH SIDES AND IN the kicking game. All
right. I thought the turning point in
the game, all right, was the turnover
that we ended up creating defensively
where it really opened it up. Where's uh
where's Kev at?
>> All right, here we go. I got one I got a
couple game balls. All right, but I felt
this guy's presence all day ended up
forcing the fumble that L man ended up
getting firing.
Hey, this guy made a couple great runs.
Got his first career touchdown.
Love this guy here, Blake Corman.
>> Hey, another play that we HAD TO HAVE
GETTING A SACK. ALL RIGHT, first career
sack AS A RAM. EVEN DREW the penalty.
WHERE'S JOSIAH?
GOT A COUPLE more right here. Hey, first
touchdown as a Ram. Did his thing. Made
his presence all day. All right. WHERE
IS DEVONTE ADAMS?
>> There's a lot of guys that I can really
recognize, okay? But I KNOW WE ALL LOVE
THIS GUY. THIS IS HIS HOMETOWN. He does
so many great things for us. Wears so
many hats. I'd be lost without him. We
love him. Where's Carter Crunch?
>> RAMS ON THREE. RAMS ON THREE. ONE, TWO,
THREE.
>> BRING IT UP. BRING it up. BRING IT UP.
BRING IT UP. HERE WE GO. HEY, I WON'T BE
LONG, MAN. I CAN'T TELL YOU ENOUGH. ALL
RIGHT. HOW PROUD I AM OF THE RESILIENCE,
THE WAY THAT YOU GUYS JUST FOUGHT, THE
WAY WE RESPONDED. Give it up for
yourselves.
Hey, there is not one GUY THAT I CAN
HIGHLIGHT BECAUSE SO MANY GUYS WERE
INSTRUMENTAL IN us being able to get
that one right there. All right, but it
took All right, all of us together.
That's what it looks like. I'm really
proud of you guys, man. And hey, we'll
enjoy this for a short amount of time
and then you guys get your ass ready for
recovery. First place in the division on
the line.
HEY, LOVE YOU GUYS. MAKE SURE HEY, we
start that recovery right now. We got a
great challenge. We'll turn this Who
said that? Hey, you ready?
All right, man. Way to ruin the mood,
right?
All right. Hey, unbelievable job. All
right, but get yourselves turned over
and recovered right here. You guys will
end up having a little lift tomorrow.
We'll come back in on Tuesday. We'll be
ready to roll. Like I said, man, there's
something about this team. I love you
guys. All right. So proud of you guys.
Let's just keep building together, man.
One day at a time. Matthew Stafford, get
one
today, man. Battle. We know we got to
turn this thing around quick. Do it
again Thursday, huh?
>> Win on three. 1 2 3.
>> I'll tell you what WE'RE NOT GOING TO DO
IS EVER TAKE FOR GRANTED FINDING A WAY
TO BE ABLE TO GET A WIN. GIVE IT UP FOR
YOURSELVES FOR THAT.
HEY, couple guys. I I THOUGHT REALLY
AFTER we settled in defensively, it was
AN UNBELIEVABLE PERFORMANCE BY YOU GUYS.
SNAP IN, SNAP OUT. I THOUGHT THE EDGE
GUYS MADE THEIR PRESENCE FELT. JARED,
I got two more guys ON DEFENSE I WANT TO
RECOGNIZE. All right. This guy ended up
making his pick from recovery.
Where's Captain Lake at
all? Hey, in most Rams tackles, all
right, in history in one game, Nate L.
>> THIS GUY JUST MOVED INTO NINTH ALL TIME
IN PASS YARDS, PASSING Dan Marino.
And then one more. DREW'S GOING TO SPEND
A LOT OF MONEY ON THAT BY WHERE SHE
break down.
>> Let's get it. Now, boys, man. Let's get
it. Rounds on three. 1 2 3.
I am so proud of this football team and
WHAT YOU GUYS DID AND HOW THAT WEEK OF
work translated. YOU DON'T JUST SHOW UP
AND DO THOSE THINGS. That was a
translation of everything you guys did
throughout the course of the week. MAN,
I GOT TWO GAME BALLS. All right. Want to
be able to recognize two guys right
here. NOT ONE, NOT TWO, but three
tighties. Where's Devonte?
>> Hey, he had three to Devonte and two
more. Five Tutties. GRATEFUL FOR THIS
GUY. LEAD THE WAY. MATTHEW,
>> that's a RESILIENT GROUP. GOOD.
>> RAND ON THREE. 1 2 3.
>> Everybody get in here tight.
>> Hey, I'll tell you what. Really, we are
starting to learn how WE CAN REALLY PUT
IT TOGETHER when you look like. ALL
RIGHT. WHAT YOU GUYS LOOKED LIKE. I
MEAN, THERE ARE SO MANY STOPS that
defense is getting. Forcing turnovers on
the Viper by you, Kobe. FORBES BEING
ABLE TO GET HIS FIRST PICK. GIVE IT UP
FOR
>> FORBES.
Awesome job.
>> Hey, how about that man getting another
ONE, MAN?
I THOUGHT OFFENSIVELY YOU GUYS DID A
GREAT JOB BEING able to control the
game. Get up for the O line, man.
Tough week being able to sustain
possession. ALL RIGHT. SO, WHAT WE'LL DO
TOMORROW, YOU GUYS WILL COME IN. WE'LL
end up being able to just get a lift
swap. You guys will just get a lift.
Carter will send it out. We're not We'll
end up cleaning up this film on
Wednesday. Get you guys in and out just
being able to look at it. So modified.
All right. Victory Monday.
>> Guys got to be ABLE TO SIGN AUTOGRAPHS.
VICTORY MONDAY NIGHT.
>> NOPE. HEY, LISTEN. All right. In all
seriousness though, I'm so proud of this
football team. We got a big one coming
up this week. All right. Great
opportunity to really just keep building
on the momentum you guys have built. You
can feel what it's like the way that you
guys have been preparing, the way that
you guys have been enjoying it, but the
appropriate urgency. It's not by mistake
why things have looked the way they've
looked. All right. Keep mindset. Keep
that mentality. I love this team, man.
So grateful to be part of it. Always.
Hey, we're going to have a lot of guys
that we'll recognize at the appropriate
time. But when you talk about greatness
over time, top 10 now, eighth all time
in receiving touchdowns at 109. Give it
up for Devonte.
>> Say no, we doing our thing. Hey, keep
keep going, man. Rest of this year, keep
our heads down. do what we do. Let's go.
tight. I won't be long. Great job. Great
team win, man. THAT TOOK EVERYBODY. SO
PROUD OF YOU GUYS. Ninth QV to go over
400 ALL TIME. ALL RIGHT, MATTHEW
STAFFORD.
Let's go. Hey, great job today, MAN.
LOVE PLAYING WITH YOU GUYS. IT'S a hell
of a lot of fun, man. Let's get it going
for NEXT WEEK, HUH? RAMS ON 3. 1 2 3.
>> HOW ABOUT THAT?
intercept
at where's D will at man will got one.
GREAT JOB. WHERE'S THE LAND SHARK?
>> Awesome job right there. You know what,
man? I'm so proud of you guys. All
right. Hey, how about this? THOUSANDTH
CAREER CATCH RIGHT THERE. DEVONTE HAD
another
>> tell you this. THIS IS A GREAT EXAMPLE
OF BEING ABLE TO PICK one another up.
HEY, HOW ABOUT ETHAN EVANS PUTTING IT ON
THE P.
>> Never take for granted finding a way.
Just being able toing be SO RESILIENT
DEFENSIVELY. WHAT A BLESSING OFFENSIVELY
FOR US TO BE ABLE TO learn from this and
continue to grow. But man, this group
finding different ways to be able to
win. Can't say enough about it. CAM
KITCHENS, GET ONE, BABY.
>> HEY, THAT'S MAN. ON ME. 1 2 3.
>> HEY, THAT WAS A OUTSTANDING JOB. RIGHT
FROM THE JUMP, YOU GUYS CAME READY TO
GO. GIVE IT UP FOR YOURSELVES. ALL
RIGHT. HEY, a lot of guys that we'll
recognize, but I thought this game, this
play ENDED UP REALLY OPENING THE GAME
UP. Huge play. ANOTHER BIG WEEK RIGHT
THERE. WHERE'S ELENA SHARP?
>> Tied an NFL record, 27 touchdowns
without an interception.
>> Give it up for our guy Matthew.
>> Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Man,
>> that's a great game, man. Love being a
part of this team, man. Let's get it
going next week. HUH? LET'S GO. RAMS ON
THREE. ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> HEY, HEY, got it in full, guys. I want
to be able to recognize. All right, but
this is the greatest team sport that
there is, but I want to be able to
recognize obviously I was sick over the
last couple days. This guy and the
offensive staff did a hell of a job
today. Where's Give me Mike Lafleur.
Where's
First career interception as a Ram just
continuing to get turnovers late.
>> This really is for the whole offensive
line to be able to recognize these guys.
Over 200 on the
Hey, and then you go 12 for 128, two
touchdowns. Big time day for Blake
Corum.
Hey, first actually surprising to hear
this. This guy just continued to do
unbelievable stuff, but first
multi-touchdown game. Did his damn thing
again. Puking the
Hey, I pray you don't get what I just
said.
>> Hey, and we love this guy, man. Just
leading us, doing a great job stacking
another great performance. Matthew
Stafford,
>> hey, I appreciate it, man. I love you
guys, man. Let's keep going. Huh? Rams
on 3. ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> HEY GUYS. HEY. Here's what I'm going to
tell YOU GUYS. SO PROUD OF THE
RESILIENCE, the mental toughness, and
here's the reality. All right. You might
We punched our ticket to BE ABLE TO GET
IN THE PLAYOFFS, BUT WE KNOW. GOOD JOB.
RIGHT. Excellent job. WE DIDN'T TALK
ABOUT THAT ALL WEEK, BUT WE KNEW THIS.
ALL RIGHT. UNBELIEVABLE JOB. I'LL
RECOGNIZE A COUPLE GUYS, BUT OUR
PREPARATION FOR THURSDAY starts right
after this. All right. GET THAT
RECOVERY. GET YOURSELF RIGHT. THAT WAS A
PHYSICAL GAME. ALL RIGHT. BUT I'VE BEEN
WAITING TO BE ABLE TO GIVE A COUPLE OF
THESE GUYS THESE GAME BALLS. ALL RIGHT.
OUR ASSISTANT HEAD COACH HAS HISTORY
THERE. LOVE THIS GUY. WHAT A LEADER.
WHAT A STUD. WHERE'S
>> KOBE PARKINSON KRON WILLIAMS HAD A
COUPLE TOUCHDOWNS.
That's unreasonable. All right. But hey,
NEW CAREER HIGH 181 WAS ALL OVER the
place today.
>> You already know the man right there.
>> Hey man, I love coming to work with you
guys, man. Let's keep kicking ass, huh?
Got a game. Feels like 72. Let's go get
IT DONE. HUH?
>> RAMS ON 3. 1 2 3.
>> All right, GUYS. I WON'T BE LONG. BRING
IT UP. BRING IT UP. BRING IT UP. BRING
IT UP. BRING IT UP. HEY, I'LL TELL YOU
GUYS THIS. ALL RIGHT. THAT WAS AN
AWESOME JOB. WE go down three points.
And what I felt from us was that sense
of urgency, the enjoyment, and the
urgency. And then the next thing you
know, WE'RE GETTING STOP AFTER STOP.
WE'RE MAKING THE PLAYS we need to make
on teams. Three straight touchdown
drives and you finish the game. That's
what it's going to take moving forward.
All right. THAT KIND OF MINDSET AND
mentality when things get tight and now
what a awesome opportunity that we got
in front of us. All right. Hey, the
playoffs start now. Go. All right. Let's
go. I got one game ball. All right.
Where is Where's it at? Right here. All
right. Hey, guy moved into sixth in
completions all time. Seventh in TDs
PASS DAN MARINO. NO DOUBT OUR MVP. LET'S
GO.
MVP MVP MVP MVP MVP.
>> HEY, TWO MORE GAME BALLS. HOW ABOUT ONE
FOR FOR MCVEY FOR UH LESS KNEE 100TH
CAREER WIN. LET'S GO.
>> Let's go. Let me tell YOU SOMETHING.
HEY, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT. I LOVE THIS
TEAM. All right. Hey, one day at a time.
TOTALLY AND COMPLETELY PRESENT. FAMILY
ON THREE. 1 2 3
MVP MVP MVP.
>> Hey, we earned the right to do it again,
man. Let's keep earning that right every
day, right? Love coming to work with
this, man. Let's get that going, HUH?
>> ON THREE. 1 2 3.
>> THERE WERE SO MANY THINGS THAT WENT ON
IN THAT GAME that you could have said,
"Oh, man. Maybe tonight's not our
night." But I'm going to tell you this
though. For you guys to do what you did,
man. I I CAN'T SAY ENOUGH ABOUT WHAT you
guys did. Snap in, snap out defensively.
How about my mother man Cam girl?
AND THEN HEY, FINDING A WAY TO END THE
MOTHER. Where's me?